[ Music ]
［ 音乐 ］
[ Applause ]
［ 掌声 ］
>> Good afternoon everyone.
>> 大家下午好
My name is John Hess.
我是 John Hess
Today I'm going to be joined by
今天我将和 Matthew Lucas 一起
to be talking to all of you
与在座的各位
about practical approaches to
谈谈提高 App 性能的
great app performance.
一些实用的方法
Now, I'm an engineer on the
我现在是一名 Xcode 团队的工程师
Xcode team, and I've had the
在过去的七年
luxury of spending the last
我有幸一直专注于
several years focused on
提高性能的工作
First, with Project Find, and
首先是在 Xcode 的两个领域
Open Quickly, two areas of Xcode
“Project Find” 和 “Open Quickly”
that treat performance as the
二者的主要功能 都是提高性能
Most recently, I've had the
最近 我有机会去
opportunity to do a survey of
做一项关于
Xcode GY responsiveness, and I
Xcode GY 响应性的调查
want to share with you the
我想与你们分享的是
approaches that I take to
在进行性能工作时
performance work, both in code
我所使用的方法
that I'm intimately familiar
其中包括我十分熟悉的代码
with, and in code that I'm just
也包括我
experiencing for the first time.
第一次接触到的代码
Now, if I could get everyone in
那么 如果各位想从今天的演讲中有所收获
today's presentation to just
我希望各位至少能
take one lesson away, it is that
记住一点 那就是
all of your performance work
你们所有提高性能的工作
should be based on measurement.
都要基于测量的结果
Before you start solving a
在开始解决一个性能问题时
performance problem, you should
你需要进行测量
measure, to establish a baseline
来建立一个基线
so you know where you stand.
让你知道自己所处的位置
As you iterate on solving a
当你重复解决
performance problem, you should
同一个性能问题时
measure it each step of the way
你应该测量每一步所使用的方法
to ensure that your performance
以确保性能的改变
changes are having the impact
能够带来你所期待的效果
When you're done solving a
当你解决了一个性能问题
performance problem, you should
你还需要再测量一遍
measure again, so that you can
这样你可以与原先的基线
compare to your original
进行对比
baseline, and make a quantified
从而给出一个量化的结果
claim about just how much you've
关于你将 App 的性能
improved the performance of your
真正提高了多少
You want to share this with your
你想要将成果报告给你的老板
boss, your colleagues, and your
分享给你的同事和用户
Now, when you think about
那么 当你想要为你的用户提高性能时
users, you need to think about
你需要考虑这一点
what I like to call the total
我喜欢称它为
performance impact.
总体性能影响
If you improve the functionality
如果你将 App 的
and performance of one area of
一个领域的性能
your application, by 50%, but
提高了 50%
it's something that just 1% of
但你的用户
your users encounter, that does
只体验到了其中的 1%
not have nearly the breadth of
那么这种提升的影响广度
impact as improving some other
还不及你只提高了其他领域的 10%
feature by just 10% that all of
但所有用户都能体验到
your users use all the time.
这全部的 10%
So make sure you're not
所以一定不要去优化边缘的案例
sure that your changes are
要确保你的性能的优化
impacting all of your users.
能够为全部的用户所体验
Now how do we fix performance
那么我们如何修复
bugs?
性能漏洞呢
Well, how do we fix regular
如何修复常规的漏洞呢
Normally it starts with some
一般来说 最开始用户反馈给我们
sort of defect report from
某方面的缺陷报告
users, and we take this report
我们接收到这个报告
of the application not behaving
了解到用户对 App 的性能
the way that people expect, and
有一些不满意的地方
we find some way to synthesize
于是我们会设法
steps to reproduce so that we
来综合步骤进行故障重现
can cause the failure at will.
以便我们可以随意地使程序出错
Once we've done this, we attach
一旦我们成功的做到 我们就给
a debugger to our program, so
程序附加一个调试器
that we can see just what our
以便我们看到我们的程序出错的时候
misbehaving.
在做什么
We combine that with our
再结合我们的知识
knowledge of how the code is
想想代码应该如何工作
supposed to work, to modify it
在必要时修改它
as necessary and eliminate the
来消除那些
undesired behavior.
不如意的部分
We verify that we haven't
我们要确保我们没有
introduced any unwanted side
带来任何不想要的副作用
effects, and we repeat as
同时 要进行必要的重复
necessary until we've completely
直到我们完全地
solved the bug.
解决了这个漏洞
I've fixed performance bugs in
我已经用相同的方法
just the same way.
修复了许多性能漏洞
Except instead of using a
只不过我并没有使用调试器
debugger, I use a profiler, and
而是使用了一个分析器
a profiler is just a fancy tool
分析器就是一个很好的测量工具
I find some set of steps to
我用一些步骤
reproduce the program being
来重现运行很慢的
slow.
程序
And I run those steps with a
我用一个附加的分析器
profiler attached, so that I can
来执行这些步骤
get an insight into what my code
因此我可以深入地了解
is doing while it's running
当我的代码运行缓慢时
slowly.
它发生了什么
I combine that knowledge with
然后再结合
what my program has to do to
我的程序必须要如何运行
accomplish the task at hand, and
才能完成手边的任务
I find steps that are happening
我找到其中正在进行的步骤
and remove them, because the
并删除了它们
primary way you make your code
因为想让你的代码变快的
faster is you remove redundant
首要方法就是删除多余的步骤
steps from whatever is that is
无论它正在计算的是什么
Now, I make the modifications to
现在 我修改了源代码
the source code, and I repeat
在必要时进行反复测量
and measure as necessary until
直到我对整体的结果
I'm happy with the total result.
感到满意为止
When I'm doing this type of
当我通过这种方法提高性能时
myself in one of a handful of
我发现自己常常处于
scenarios.
一些场景当中
And these different scenarios
这些不同的场景
change the way that I go about
改变了我测试有问题代码的方式
testing the code in question to
以及复制这些
reproduce the bugs.
漏洞的方法
Sometimes I'm up against a big
有时我会遇到
performance regression, right?
严重的性能衰退问题 对吗
Everything was moving along
开始一切都在平稳地运行
smoothly, then someone checked
然后我们的团队里
something in on our team, maybe
有人对其进行了检测
it was me, and performance has
这个人也许是我
fallen through the floor, and
然后发现性能出现了严重的衰退
now we have to go back and find
那么我们就需要回去
out what caused this regression.
找出这种衰退的原因
If this regression is very
如果这种衰退十分明显
pronounced, or it's in an area
或者是它出现在一个
that I don't think it's likely
我认为近期
to regress again in the
不可能再次衰退的地方
immediate future, I may just
我也许会自己手动地
test it with my hands, manually,
运用附加的分析器
with the profiler attached.
对它进行测试
However, your performance
但是 想提高你的性能
victories are going to be
这是一个不大容易的过程
hard-won battles, and they can
因为很可能
easily be lost through a slow
只是一系列轻微的衰退
stream of regressions.
就会让你功亏一篑
I would encourage all of you to
我建议你们所有人
write automated performance
创建自动化的性能测试
tests to capture your app's
来捕捉你的 App 的性能
performance, so that you can
这样你就可以
ensure that it's not regressing
保证它不会随着时间而衰退
Another scenario I often find
我经常所处的另一个场景是
myself in, is, are applications
App 的性能
performing the same as it has
在很长一段时间后
been for a long time?
还能保持不变吗
Maybe it is running at 45 frames
也许在一些绘图测试中
a second in some drawing test,
它运行的速度是 45 帧每秒
but we expect it to run at 60.
但是我们希望的运行速度是 60 每秒
It needs to be improved
所以我们需要小幅地提高它
marginally, and we have reason
并且我们有理由相信
to believe through our previous
通过我们先前的性能工作
performance work that we can get
我们可以利用现场修复
there through spot fixes and
以及增量式变化
incremental changes.
来对它进行提高
Now, in this type of scenario, I
在这种场景下
probably also have automated
我或许也已经自动地
tests already in play, because I
开始进行测试了
understand my performance over
因为随着时间的推移
time.
我已经很了解我的性能了
And a third scenario, our
还有第三种场景
application is just suffering
我们的 App
from a poor design and
因为设计不良而受到损害
performance is orders of
性能也远远比不上
magnitude worse than it should
它原应达到的效果
We know that we can't improve it
我们知道我们不能用
with simple spot fixes, because
简单的场地修复来提高性能
we've tried them in the past,
因为过去我们这么尝试过
and we are still stuck here with
但并没有成功
a very sub-par performance.
无法提高性能
In a situation like this, you'd
在这样的情况下
want to do a total performance
你会想要做一次彻底的性能检修
redesigning some core part of
你会想重新设计一些特性的核心部分
the feature, or the algorithms
或是有问题的算法
in question, so that performance
以使性能成为一个
is a primary constraint.
首要的约束条件
And definitely in these cases,
在这些情况里
you would have performance tests
你必然要对性能进行检测
to measure that you're actually
以测量你确实
hitting your performance
达到了你的性能目标
Now, it is important that you
知道你要测试什么 很重要
I want to caution you that I
我想要提醒你的是
don't ever immediately jump to
我从来都不会立刻投入
these sort of performance
这些性能检修
overhauls as a way of fixing a
将其视为解决
performance problem.
某种性能问题的方法
I love to do that.
我喜欢这么做
It's sort of Greenfield
这是一种未曾开发的工程
engineering, where you get to
你能够从头开始 设计这些东西
up, but it's very risky.
但这也颇具风险
You're going to end up with a
你最终要的是
better product at the end, but
一个性能更好的产品
it's going to be a turbulent
但这却是一个曲折的过程
path getting there as you rework
因为你需要重新设计
an entire feature.
整个特性
When you're doing this style of
当你做这种工作的时候
work, it is imperative you
你不仅需要知道
understand not only the
这些代码的
functional constraints of the
功能约束条件
code in question, but also the
你还要知道
performance constraints, and the
性能约束条件
typical use patterns that your
以及你的用户应用这一特性时
users are most frequently
最常使用的
applying to this feature, and
典型的模式
you only get that by having done
而你只能从
performance work in the area in
过去这方面的性能工作中
the past.
获得这方面信息
I'd like to share an anecdote
我想和你们分享一件轶事
about our work on a situation
是我们的一个
like this, within Xcode.
在 Xcode 里工作的案例
In Xcode 9, we reworked Project
在 Xcode 9 中 我们重做了 “Project Find”
Find, with performance as a
将性能作为一个
primary goal.
首要的目标
It was our goal to deliver
我们的目标就是要
search results in just tens of
在短短几十毫秒中
milliseconds.
传递出搜索结果
When we were going to discuss
当我们与同事
this feature with our
讨论这个特性时
colleagues, we were often
我们常常遇到一些挑战
challenged to perform searches
比如让我们在一些大的项目上
across large projects for things
搜索一些类似于字符串
like string, or even the letter
或者甚至是字母 E
E.
这样的东西
Things that produce millions of
这些东西能搜索出成千上万种结果
results, right?
不是吗
And certainly if our application
当然如果你的 App
could produce millions of
能够迅速生产出成千上万的结果
results quickly, it would be
它搜索任何东西
fast on anything.
都会很快
But if you consider what typical
但是如果你思考一下
patterns are, we search for APIs
什么是典型的模式
we use, the names of our own
我们搜索我们使用的 API
classes, the names of, you know,
我们自己的类名称
images that we're referencing.
还有我们引用的图片名称
Things like that.
诸如此类的东西
They produce dozens, maybe
它能搜索出很多结果
hundreds of results.
也许上百种结果
Certainly, it is essential that
当然十分重要的是 当有一百万种搜索结果时
the application works decently
你的 App 能够
when you get a million results,
正常地工作运转
but the normal use case is
但是通常的使用情况是
hundreds of results.
有数百种搜索结果
Now, some of your work in doing
那么 在进行搜索这样的任务时
a task like search is going to
你所做的一些工作
be proportional on things like
要与生成原始结果
generating the raw results, and
这样的东西相对应
other work is going to be based
而其余的工作则要基于
on how efficiently you can index
你能多有效地索引
the text in the project, and
项目中的文本
avoid work in the first place.
并预先避免工作
In these two scenarios, you're
在这两种场景中
likely to have completely
你可能会有完全
different targets for what you
不同的优化目标
would optimize to make one of
让其中一个目标的搜索速度
these searches faster than the
快于其他的目标 对吗
So it's essential that you
因而你有必要了解
understand how your users are
你的用户将要
going to use the product, so
如何使用该产品
that you can optimize for the
这样你就可以优化
right cases.
应该优化的案例
Now, in all of these cases, I
在所有的这些案例中
need to do some form of testing,
我需要进行一些形式的测试
whether it's manual, or
无论是手动地 还是自动地
I want to share with you two
我想要与你分享
types of performance tests that
两类典型的性能测试
I will typically write to
我通常用它们
measure the performance of
来测量 Xcode 的性能
We will either do unit tests, or
我们或者进行单元测试
integration tests.
或者进行综合测试
Let's compare and contrast them.
我们来对比一下这两种测试
In a performance unit test, it's
在性能的单元测试中
your goal to isolate some
你的目标就是对你的 App 的
feature of your application and
某些特征进行隔离
measure it all by itself.
并单独地对其进行测量
You might mock out its
你也许会抹去它的相关性
dependencies, and you might
然后在一个
launch it in a context where it
隔离的环境中
has been isolated.
启动它
If I were to write performance
如果我要为 Xcode 的代码完成
unit tests for Xcode's code
性能的单元测试
completion, I might write a
那我也许会编写
series of three small tests.
一系列的三个小测试
One of these tests would measure
其中一个测试会测量
talking to the compiler and
与编译器的对话
getting the raw results, the raw
并得到原始的结果
set of code completion
和原始的代码完成候选的结果
Another performance test would
另一个性能测试则会测量
measure correlating, ranking and
那些结果的相互关联
scoring those results, so we
对它们进行排列以及评分
knew which ones to display to
以便我们知道要将哪些结果
the user.
显示给用户
A third test might take those
第三个测试会选取
already prepared results, and
那些已经准备好的结果
measure putting them into UI
并测量将它们放入 UI 元素
elements for final display.
后最终展示出来的情况
And in covering all three of
为了涉及到全部三个方面
these areas, I would have pretty
我会很好地覆盖 IDE 中
components of code completion in
代码完成的主要的组件
Now, there are some great
这些性能单元测试
aspects to these performance
有一些很好的方面
They're going to be highly
我们将高度聚焦这些方面
focused, which means if they
这意味着如果它们
regress in the future, I'm going
在将来出现衰退
to have a very good idea on
我会很清楚地知道
where the regression is, because
这些衰退出现在哪里
the code that is running has
因为这些正在运行的代码
been scoped so well.
已经处于检查之中了
They are also going to produce
而它们也将在不断地运行过程中
much more repeatable results
产生出更多的
from run to run.
可重复的结果
They're not going to have a big
而它们产生的时间
variance in the times that they
也不会有太大的波动
Again, because the code is so
因为这些代码
focused.
是高度聚焦的
Now, let's contrast that to an
现在 我们来将单元测试与
integration test.
综合测试进行对比
In an integration test, your job
在综合测试中
is to measure the performance of
你要做的是
your application as your users
在用户使用 App 时
experience it.
对其性能进行全面地测量
So, if I was writing code
所以 如果我为 Xcode 编写
completion unit tests for Xcode,
代码完成单元测试
I'm sorry, integration tests, I
哦不对 是综合测试
would launch the full Xcode app.
我会启动全部的 Xcode App
I would open a source file.
我会打开一个源文件
I would navigate to the source
我会定位到该源文件
file, and I would type, and I
然后进行书写
would bring up code completion
再反复地进行代码完成
When I profile this, to see what
当我执行这些步骤的时候
Xcode is doing, and how much
看看 Xcode 在做什么
time it is taking, I am going to
看看它花了多少时间
find that this test is anything
我会发现这个测试 一点也不聚焦
Xcode is going to be doing
Xcode 会在我书写的时候
drawing and layout as I type.
进行绘制和布局
It is going to be doing syntax
当我归类时 它还会同时进行语法着色
In the background, it might be
在后台 Xcode 也许正在进行索引
indexing, fetching get status,
读取获取状态 并决定把新的文件
deciding to show new files in
显示在 Assistant Editor 中
and all of these things are
而所有的这些
going to be competing for CPU
都将与代码完成一起
resources, along with code
来竞争 CPU 的资源
Maybe when I look in the
也许当我查看 Profiler 时
Profiler, I'll see that we spend
我会看到我们花费了
80% of our time syntax coloring,
80% 的时间在做语法着色
and 20% of our time in code
而剩下的 20% 则用在了代码完成上
And with this data, I would know
从这个数据我可以知道
that the best way to improve
要提高代码完成性能
code completion performance
最好的方法就是
would be to defer syntax
推迟语法着色
I will never gain that type of
这样的知识
knowledge with a highly focused
是我在高度聚焦的单元测试中
unit test.
所无法获得的
So if I can get everyone here to
所以如果今天各位听完这个演讲
take two things away from this
只能带走两样东西的话
presentation, the second one
第二样就是
should be that your performance
要调查你的性能
investigations should absolutely
必然应该从这些
start with these wide
广泛的综合测试开始
integration tests that measure
它们会测量你的用户
how the users experience your
使用 App 时的用户体验
So I'm talking about testing,
对 我说的就是测试
measuring and profiling.
测量以及分析
And right now, I'd like to
现在我想向你们
introduce you to profiling in
介绍一下用工具
Xcode with instruments.
在 Xcode 中进行分析
Let's head over to the demo
让我们来看一下
machine.
demo machine
Today we are going to be looking
今天我们要看的是一个
at a performance problem that we
我们在 Xcode 9 和
fixed between Xcode 9 and Xcode
Xcode 10 之间修复了的性能问题
10.
我想展示给你们
I'm going to launch Xcode 9, and
下面我先启动 Xcode 9
open our solar system
打开我们的 Solar System App
Now the problem that we are
那么 我们所
going to be looking at is
面临的问题就是创建标记
I'm going to just press
接着我要快速地
Command-T quickly a couple of
按几下快捷键 “Command-T”
times, and as you can see, the
如你所见
whole screen flashes black, and
整个屏幕闪现了黑色
it takes several seconds to
并且创建这些标记
create those tabs.
花了好几秒的时间
That definitely doesn't meet my
这肯定达不到
expectations as far as
我对性能的预期
performance goes, and we need to
我们需要来对它进行修复
So let's take a look at how you
那么我们来看看
would do that.
如何进行修复
First, I'm going to launch
首先 我将启动 Instruments
Instruments.
这是我们的分析工具
You can do that from the Xcode
你可以从 Xcode 菜单中打开它
menu, under Open Developer Tool,
在 Instruments 中的
Instruments.
Open Developer Tool 里面
Now, I'm currently in Xcode 9,
现在 我在 Xcode 9 里面
so if I choose this, it's going
所以如果我选择这个选项
to launch the Instruments from
那我启动的是
Xcode 9, and of course, I want
Xcode 9 中的 Instruments
the Instruments from Xcode 10,
当然我想要从 Xcode 10 中启动 Instruments
which I've put here in my doc.
我已经把我的文件放在这里了
So I'm going to hide Xcode, and
我将隐藏 Xcode
bring up Instruments.
打开 Instruments
Now, when Instruments launches,
当 Instruments 启动时
we're presented with a list of
就会出现一系列的分析工具
profiling tools that we could
我们可以用它们
use to measure our application.
测量我们的 App
There's all kinds of tools here.
这里是各种各样的工具
They can measure graphics
它们能够测量
utilization, memory consumption,
图形的利用率 内存消耗
IO, and time in general.
IO 以及整体的时间
It can be intimidating to know
你们也许会对从哪个工具
which one of these profilers to
先开始学习
start with.
而感到不安
I would encourage all of you, if
那么我对你们的建议是
you just learn one of these
如果只学习其中的一个工具
tools, it should be the Time
那么你们应该学习
Profiler.
Time Profiler
I use it for 95% or more of my
在我的性能工作中
performance work.
有 95% 甚至更多的情况下都在使用它
When your users complain about
当你的用户抱怨
your app being slow, they're
你的 App 运行很慢时
complaining about it taking too
他们是在抱怨
long, and long is time.
它花费了太多的时间
If it turns out that you're slow
假如你的 App 太慢了
because you're doing too much
是因为你运行了太多的 IO
IO, that is going to correlate
从而花费了太多的时间
with time, and you will be able
那么你就能在 Time Profiler
to see this with the Time
上看到这一点
Profiler.
所以如果你只学习一个工具
instrument, it should be the
那就学 Time Profiler
Let's take a look at how that
我们来看看它是如何工作的
I'm going to launch the Time
我要启动 Time Profiler
Profiler by just double clicking
只需要双击这里
on it here, and make Instruments
然后将 Instruments
take the full best op.
全屏显示
Now, we'd like to record Xcode.
下面 我想要记录 Xcode
In the upper left-hand corner of
在 Instruments 视窗的左上角
the Instruments window, you can
你可以控制
control which process you're
你想要附加和记录的进程
By default, hitting this record
在默认情况下 只要按下这个记录按钮
button would record all
我的 Mac 上的所有进程
processes on my Mac.
都会被记录
I just want to focus on Xcode.
而我只想锁定到 Xcode
I'll switch this popover to
我会将这个弹出框
Xcode and hit record.
切换到 Xcode 然后点击记录
Now, I like to keep an eye on
现在 当我记录的时候
this area of the window to track
我就要关注视窗中的这个区域
view while I'm recording.
来追踪轨迹视图
So I'm going to resize the Xcode
我要调整 Xcode 视窗的大小
window to be a little shorter,
将它调小一点
so I can still see that, and
我就能看到那个区域
then I'm going to do the thing
然后我就要进行让它变慢的操作
I'm going to create a couple
我要多创建几个标记
And you can see the graph
你可以看到这里的图表 发生了变化
Now, I'm going to go ahead and
现在 我要退出 App
quit, and return to Instruments.
然后回到 Instruments
So what just happened?
所以刚刚发生了什么
While the Profiler was running,
当分析器在运行时
it was attached to our process
它被附加在我们的进程之中
like a debugger.
像一个调试器
And it stopped it, thousands of
这个分析器每秒钟
times per second, and as it was
都数千次地停止
stopping it, it gathered back
我们的进程 并且它采集了跟踪轨迹
Now, just a reminder, a back
那么 提醒一下
trace is a description of how
跟踪轨迹描述了
your program got to where it
你的程序如何到达
currently is.
它目前所处的位置
So if you're on line 6 of
所以如果你现在
function C and you got there
处于 C 函数的第 6 行
because main called A, called B,
你到达那里的原因是因为 Main 函数调用了 A B C
called C, then your back trace
那么你的跟踪轨迹就是 Main A B C
When Instruments captures one of
当 Instruments 捕捉到
these back traces, it notes,
这些跟踪轨迹中的其中一个时
hey, we just spent one
它会说 嘿 我们刚刚在 C 函数中
millisecond in function C.
花了一毫秒
It says one millisecond, because
它说一毫秒
that is our sampling interval
是因为我们的
for recording once every
记录采样间隔为
millisecond.
一毫秒每次
Now, on the main thread, all
那么 在主线程上
these back traces are going to
所有的这些跟踪轨迹都要
start with the Main function,
从 Main 函数开始
and they're probably going to
它们也许将要调用
call Application Main, and
Application Main
they're going to branch out, all
之后它们将会通过你的源代码
through your source code after
不断地进行扩展
We can collapse these back
我们可以将这些跟踪轨迹
traces together, and overlay
折叠在一起
them into a prefix tree, so they
将它们覆盖放进一个前缀树
start at Main and work their way
以便它们从 Main 开始 进行下去
out.
我们可以将我们
millisecond counters that we
捕捉到的这些毫秒计数器
captured at the top, so that we
放在顶端 这样我们就能够
can hierarchically see how much
看到在我们源代码的
time was spent in all the
所有不同层级的区域上
different areas of our source
我们都花费了多少时间
And we are going to look at this
我们要看看这个数据
data to try and find redundant
试着找出多余的
and unnecessary operations that
和不必要的操作
we can make faster, and that is
这样我们就可以提高速度
our primary method that we are
这是我们提高
going to use to improve the
App 性能的
performance of our application.
首要方法
Now, as you can imagine, we're
现在 正如你能想象到那样
capturing thousands of back
我们每秒能捕捉
traces per second.
上千的跟踪轨迹
There is an overwhelming amount
在 Instruments 里
of data for you to wade through
有大量的数据需要你去处理
My primary advice to you is that
我首先要给你的建议就是
you want to filter this data as
你想要尽可能多地
much as possible so that you can
过滤这里的数据
see the course grain performance
你需要看整个过程的性能
leads, and not focus on minutia.
不要把精力集中在细节点上
All right?
好吧
So I want to show you how to
我想要给你演示
apply a bunch of powerful
如何应用一堆强大的过滤器和工具
So as I did the recording, you
因为我之前做了记录
remember, I had the track view
还记得吧 我让轨迹视图显示了出来
I did that because I wanted to
我这么做是因为我想要
see how the CPU utilization
看看当我创建标记的时候
changed and where it was
CPU 的利用率是如何变化的
changing, while I was creating
以及在哪里发生了变化
new tabs, and I noted to myself
然后我告诉自己
that it was right here.
就在这儿
I simply dragged and selected
我只是拖动鼠标并选中了
over that area of the trace, and
轨迹所在的区域
I've caused instruments to only
我让 Instruments
focus its back trace data on
将它的跟踪轨迹数据只专注于
just that time interval.
那里的时间间隔上
Everything over here, this is
所有在这里的东西
before I was creating tabs.
都是我创建标记之前的
after I was creating tabs, when
都是我创建了标记
I was quitting the application.
退出 App 之后的
That's not what I'm trying to
那不是我现在要优化的地方
optimize right now, so I don't
所以我不需要
need to see that data.
看那里的数据
Now, in the bottom area of the
现在 在 Instruments 视窗的底部区域
Instruments window, Instruments
Instruments 会显示出所有它
is showing me all the traces it
所采集到的轨迹
By default, there is one row per
默认情况下
thread that was running.
每个线程上只有一行在运作
And in this example it looks
在这个例子里
like there was only four threads
看起来只有四个线程在运作
Sometimes you'll have much more.
而有时候则会更多
Depends on how concurrent your
这取决于你的 App
application is.
是如何并行的
I often like to collapse these
我通常喜欢以聚焦的名义
also like to collapse them so
我也喜欢折叠它们
they're based on the top level
让他们建立在每个线程中的
functions executing in each of
函数执行的最顶层上
the threads, rather than the
而不是线程 ID 上
thread IDs, because that
因为前者与我使用
corresponds better with how I
Grand Central Dispatch 的方式
use Grand Central Dispatch.
更为契合
Down in the bottom of the
接下来我们看看
Instruments window, I'm going to
Instruments 视窗的底部
click on this button that says
我要点击这个叫 Call Tree 的按钮
Call Tree, and I'm going to zoom
然后放大它
in on it, so you can see what
这样你就能看到
I'm about to do.
我要做什么了
There are several filters
这里有几个可用的过滤器
One of them is separate by
其中一个被线程分开了
thread.
默认情况下它就已经开启了
I am going to go ahead and
接下来我要禁用它
disable that, and instead, all
相反地 所有的线程都将按照
grouped by their top level entry
它们的最顶层入口点来分组
point, rather than their thread
而不是它们的线程 ID
Now, looking at this trace, I
现在 来看这个轨迹
can see that of all these
可以看到所有这些
threads running, which by the
正在运作的线程 顺便提一下
way, below the main trace, which
在主要轨迹的下面
is the aggregate CPU usage, the
是总的 CPU 使用率
CPU usage is broken down per
CPU 使用率被分解到每一个线程上
thread, I can see that almost
我们可以看到在这个轨迹中
all the other threads were
几乎其他所有的线程
largely inactive during this
大部分都是闲置的
I can focus on just the main
我可以只聚焦主线程
thread by selecting it here, and
从这里选择它
now I'm only looking at traces
现在我们就可以只看
from the main thread during this
在这个时间段内
time period.
主线程的轨迹
I'm ready to start digging into
我准备开始深入到
this call hierarchy, so I can
这个调用层级当中
see what my application was
这样就能看到我的 App
doing.
在做什么
Often, I'll walk this with the
通常我会键入这一过程
keyboard, by just pressing right
只要按下向右箭头和向下箭头
arrow and down, over and over
然后不断地进行重复就可以了
But I'd like to show you the
但是我想要给你们演示
heaviest back trace inspector
Instruments 提供的
that Instruments offers.
最密集的跟踪轨迹检测
If your Inspector is not
如果你的检测是不可见的
visible, you can toggle it with
你可以用这个按钮
this button, and the heaviest
进行切换
back trace will be available
最密集的追踪轨迹就都会在这
here, in this tab, Extended
在这个标记里
Detail.
“Extended Detail”
Now, the heaviest back trace is
那么 最密集的追踪轨迹
just the trace that occurred
正是出现得最频繁的
most frequently.
那个轨迹
It's the back trace that
当我们在当前选择下
happened most frequently while
进行记录的时候
we were recording under the
追踪轨迹出现得最为频繁
And you can use this to quickly
你可以利用这个
navigate many frames deep at a
在一段时间内 快速浏览许多帧
I typically look through here,
我通常会浏览这里
looking for my own APIs, and
寻找我自己的 API
things that would surprise me
还有值得我花这么多时间
for taking up this amount of
来寻找的东西
time, or for areas where we make
或者是寻找
a significant branching point in
我们在样本数中
the number of samples.
有重要分支点的地方
Now, looking through here, I see
现在我们看这里
this call, which is to IDE
我看到这个给 IDE 的调用
Navigator, replacement view, did
Navigator Replacement View
install view controller.
Did Install View Controller
Now, I'm familiar with this API,
我十分熟悉这个 API
because it's an internal API of
因为这是一个 Xcode 内部的 API
And in the trace, I can see over
在这个轨迹中 我可以查看这里
here on the left-hand side of
在视窗的左手边
the window that it is
这里负责的是
responsible for 1.19 seconds of
我们记录的总时间中的
the total time we're recording,
或者 45% 的时间中的 1.19 秒
That is far and away above my
这种方法要花费的时间
expectations for how much this
远远超出了我的预期
However, it's hard to focus on
但是 我们很难聚焦在这里
what is happening here.
看看究竟发生了什么
Right? I'm, there is all this
对吗 这是这个轨迹下面的
other stuff at the bottom of the
其他所有的东西
trace, and it looks like I'm,
那么 它看起来就好像
you know, 30 or 40 stack ranges
30 到 40 的堆线范围深度
deep.
这是很吓人的
I want to show you how to focus.
我要给你演示如何聚焦这里
The first technique is back here
第一种方法就在这里
in that call tree popover again.
我们又要使用 “Call Tree” 弹出框
I'm going to use this popover to
我要在这个弹出框里
choose the flattened recursion.
选择 “flattened recursion”
Let's go ahead and do that.
让我们来继续完成这步
And now you can see that, that
现在你就可以看到
repeated set of method calls
就在这里
that was right here, oops, has
一组重复的方法调用
been collapsed.
被折叠了
I'm sorry, let me scroll down.
不好意思 让我滑下来
That has been collapsed.
它被折叠了
In fact, I'm confident that I
事实上 我就是想要
want to continue my performance
继续我的性能测试
investigation inside of this IDE
在这个 IDE Navigator 范围里
Navigator area, API call, and I
在这个 API 调用中
can refocus the entire call tree
我可以根据上下文
by context, clicking here, and
重新聚焦整个 Call Tree 点击这里
choosing Focus on Subtree.
然后选择 “Focus on Subtree”
And Instruments is going to take
之后 Instruments 就会
that symbol up to the top of the
将这个符号放到
call graph, it's going to remove
整个调用图的最顶层
everything else, and it is going
其他的所有东西都会被删除
to reset the percentages at 100%
它会重新将百分比设置为 100%
so I can focus on just this.
因此我可以就聚焦在这里
Now, I can continue to walk this
现在 我可以用键盘上的箭头键
sample with the arrow keys to
来继续运行这个样本
see what we're doing.
看看我们在做什么
And I'm familiar with these
我很熟悉这些 API
APIs.
看起来我们好像正在进行
state restoration.
状态恢复
And as I continue to expand
当我继续扩大这个
this, I can see that we are sort
我可以看到我们几乎
of deep inside the table view,
深入了这个表格视图
and in addition to there being
除了有这种
this sort of hot call path, you
热调用路径以外
know, that is taking large
你知道 这种调用路径占了
number of the total percentage,
大部分的总百分比
there's all these other
同时还有其他的这些附带样本
It's easy to get distracted by
它们很容易分散
these.
我们的注意力
One of them here is OPC Message
它们的其中之一就是
Send.
OPC Message Send
This can occur all over your
它可以遍布你的追踪器
tracers if you're writing
只要你在写 Objective C
Even if you're writing Swift
即使你在写 Swift 代码
code, as you work your way into
当你按照你的方式
the system libraries, you'll see
进入系统库时
this.
你也会看到这个
You'll often see its counterpart
你会经常看到它的对应函数
functions, OPC, Load Strong,
OPC LoadStrong LoadWeak
Load Weak, etc., Retain, you can
Retain 等等 你可以
remove all that content from the
将所有的内容从调用关系树里删除
call tree by context clicking on
根据上下文点开这里
it, and choosing Charge OPC to
选择 “Charge OPC to Callers”
That's going to tell Instruments
它就会告诉 Instruments
to take all the samples that
来选取所有
came from lib OPC and remove
来自于 OPC 库的样本
them from the call data, but
然后将它们从调用数据中删除
keep the time as attributed to
但是要将时间的属性归于
the parent frames that called
调用它们的父框架
I tend to treat those objective
我倾向于将那些
C runtime functions as just the
Objective C 运行时的函数
cost of doing business when
视为在书写 Objective C 代码时
writing objective C code.
的代价成本
It's rarely the case that I'm
我很少会去试图优化它们
them out, so I just prefer to
所以我只会
remove them from the data, so I
将它们从数据中删除
can focus on the things that I'm
这样我就可以聚焦在
likely to take action on.
我可能要处理的地方
Another very powerful filter
还有一个你们可以应用的
that you can apply, and one that
强大的过滤器
I'm going to use to remove all
我要用它来删除所有
these small samples that
出现在这一组帧中的小样本
occurred during this set of
它就在这里
frames, is here in the call tree
Call Tree 约束条件的部分
Let me show you.
让我来给你演示
I'm going to tell Instruments
我将要告诉 Instruments
that I would only like to see
我想要看到的轨迹范围
areas of the trace that
只包括我们所说的
accounted for let's say 20 or
20 或者更多的样本
I'm picking 20 because I know
我选择 20 是因为
that I've selected about a two
我知道我已经选择了
second interval and 20
一个两秒的间隔
milliseconds is going to
那么 20 毫秒
represent about 1% of the total
将会呈现出整个工作的大约 1%
work, and that is about the
而就包含了
granularity that I like to work
在默认情况下 我想进行工作的粒度
So with call tree constraints
因此将 Call Tree 约束条件
set to a minimum of 20, I now
设置为一个最小值 20
focus this down much more
我就能更有效地聚焦在这里
Now, I mentioned here that we
那么 我在这里提到过
were expanding out my view
我们在扩展我的视图项目
items.
我看到在这里
we're calling NS outline view,
我们其实在调用 NS 大纲视图
expand item, expand children.
扩展项目 扩展子项
Now, a lot of people would stop
在这里 很多人都会将调用图
point.
停在这里
They'd see I'm calling into a
我们会看到 我正在调用一个系统框架
spending a lot of time there.
我在那里花了很多时间
This isn't my fault, right?
这不是我的错 对吗
What can I do about this?
那么我能做什么呢
I can't optimize NS Outline
我不能优化 NS 大纲视图
View, Expand Items.
扩大项目
You absolutely have the power to
但你肯定有能力
influence these situations.
改变这些情况
For example, the system
例如 花费在系统框架上的
framework could be spending all
所有这些时间
of this time because it's
都是因为
operating on data that you
它在运算你提供给它的数据
It could be taking a lot of time
这需要花费很多的时间
because you are calling this
因为你在成千上万次地
method thousands or millions of
调用这个方法
It could be taking a lot of time
它会花这么多时间
because it's calling back into
还因为它还要通过授权
your code through delegation.
回调你的代码
And most importantly, you can
而最重要的是
get an insight into what the
你可以深入地了解
system framework is doing by
系统框架在做什么
expanding down through the
只要沿着 Instruments 树
Instruments tree, and looking at
不断地进行扩展
the names of functions that are
并查看这些被调用的函数的名称
In fact, that's exactly how I
其实 我就是这样学会
learned to fix this bug.
修复这个漏洞的
As I expand the trace into the
当我将这个轨迹
outline view, I can see that it
扩展到大纲视图中
is calling these two methods
我能看到 它正在调用这里的两种方法
Batch Expand Items with item
用项目入口来
entries, expand children, and do
批量处理扩展项目和子项
work after end updates.
然后再进行最后更新后的工作
Now, those are big clues to me
现在 那些对我来说都是重要的线索
that there is probably some
说明我们或许
opportunity for efficiency
有可能通过批量处理来提高效率
As you could imagine, the
正如你能想象的那样
outline view starts with a small
大纲视图从一小组项目开始
set of items, and then we are
然后我们试着
trying to restore expansion
在我们代码的这个区域内
state in this area of our code,
不断修复扩展状态
and so we are telling it to
我们会告诉它打开
open, for example, the top item.
比如说顶部的项目
And when we tell it to open the
而当我告诉它打开顶部的项目时
top item, internally you might
你能够想象
imagine that it moves all the
它同时将里面的其他项目
other items down.
都向下移了
Then you ask me to expand the
然后我继续扩展第二个项目
It moves all the items down
它就会再次下移其他项目
And the third item, and so on.
接着是第三个项目 以此类推
And by the time you're done,
而等到你做完这些
you've moved those bottom items
你已经将这些底部的项目
down thousands of times.
向下移动了数千次
That is all redundant work, and
那这些都是多余的工作
that is exactly the sort of
而它们正是
thing I'm looking to eliminate
我在提高性能时
when I'm trying to improve
想要消除的东西
Now the fact of these method
现在 这些方法调用
calls talk about batching leads
谈到的批量处理
me to believe that there is
让我觉得或许
probably some API where I can
在一些 API 中我可以
ask the outline view to do the
让大纲视图批量地进行工作
work in bulk so it computes all
因此它就可以对所有的位置
the positions just once, instead
只进行一次计算
of over and over again as I make
而不是在我进行调用的时候
the calls.
反复地计算
I also see a call that says to
我还看到一个调用
do the work after end updates.
用来进行最后更新之后的工作
Now, sometimes an API will offer
那么 有时 API 会提供那种
sort of bulk method that
在一组列阵上进行运算的
operates on an array, and other
整体方法
times, it will offer a sort of
而有时它则会提供一种
transactional API that says I'm
事务型 API
going to begin making changes,
它会说我要开始进行更改
then you make a bunch of
然后就做了一系列的变化
changes, and then you say you're
然后你说你完成了
done, and it computes something
之后它会对你变化的全程
range of your changes, more
进行计算
efficiently than if it had done
这比它自己独自完成这些
them all individually.
要更有效率
So at this point, I would head
那么这时候 我会前往
over to the NS Outline View, or
NS 大纲视图或者
NS Table View API, and I would
NS 表格视图 API
look for some such method.
我会找一些这样的方法
And there is exactly one there.
那里确实有一个
In NS Table View, there is
在 NS 表格视图里
methods for beginning and end
有一些开始和结束更新
updating, that allow the table
所使用的方法
view to coalesce, and make all
它们允许合并表格视图
this work significantly more
并能够大大提高这些工作的效率
Of course, we adopted that in
当然 我们要在 Xcode 10 中使用它
Let me show you.
让我来给你演示
I'm going to launch Xcode 10.
我要启动 Xcode 10
I'm going to open the source as
我要把 Source
an application, and I'm going to
作为一个 App 打开
create a couple of tabs.
然后我来创建一些标记
And you can see, there is no
你可以看到
awful flashing, and the tabs
这里屏幕没有出现闪黑
open much more quickly.
标记也打开得更快了
Now, I'd like the tabs to open
现在 我想让标记打开的速度
even quicker than that, right?
比这个更快 对吗
So what am I going to do next?
那么我接下来应该怎么做呢
I got lucky here.
我很幸运
It's not every day that you're
因为你不是每天
going to go into the trace, and
都需要进入轨迹中去寻找
find something so obvious and
一些如此明显且容易修复的东西
easy to fix, that is responsible
而这样的东西在样本里
for 50% of the sample.
占到了 50%
Right? In fact, there is not
对吗 其实并没有
going to be any other huge lead
什么巨大的严重问题
sitting there waiting for me.
等待我来解决
Instead, what I'm going to need
相反 我要做的其实就是
to do is go through that whole
检查整个样本
sample, with those course
并在此过程中应用过滤器
filters applied, so I'm only
所以我只是寻找
looking at operations that take
一些只占到 1% 或者更多时间的操作
and I'm going to look for every
我要寻找每一个
single thing that I see that I
我认为能够运用一些方法
think I can come up with some
来将其速度
mechanism for making a little
提高一点的东西
I'm going to note them all down
我会将它们都记下来
on a piece of paper or in a text
放在一张纸上或一个文档里
document or something, and then
或者其他什么东西上
I'm going to start solving them.
然后我就会着手解决它们
Now, I need to pick an order to
现在 我需要选择一个
solve them in, right?
解决它们的顺序 对吗
Because sometimes the fifth
因为有的时候
thing on the list, fixing it
用修复第二件事情时
with an obsolete, whatever fix
所用的方法来修复
you would do for the second
列表中的第五件事情
thing on the list, and it feels
这方法可能会是过时的
bad to do them in the wrong
如果没有排好顺序
order, such that you did
你就会做多余的工作
redundant work, because that's
这是十分糟糕的
the whole thing we're trying to
因为我们首先要删除的就是
redundant work.
多余的工作
But it's very hard to predict
但是这些工作都是如何进行的
how these things are all going
我们又很难去预测
And you often can't know until
你通常无法事先知道这些
So do not let this stop you from
所以不要因为这个
getting started, because you're
停下你开始的脚步
going to get your second 30%
因为你想要把速度提高 30%
improvement by stacking 10 3%
就得进行 103% 的
improvements.
改善工作
Okay?
明白吗
Now, I want to go back to the
现在 回到我们的幻灯片
slides, and show you some of the
我要给你演示
techniques we typically use to
一些我们常用的方法
make those continued
用来持续改善我们的性能
Far and away, the thing that
毫无疑问
comes up the most frequently is
我们最常见的就是
using those same techniques the
使用那些与大纲视觉里
outline view was using.
相同的方法
Batching and deferring, right?
批量处理和推迟处理 对吗
You have an API, and when the
你有一个 API
API is called, it has some side
而当这个 API 被调用时
effect.
会出现一些副作用
And then you have some code
然后你用一些代码
calling your API in the loop.
调用你在循环中的 API
That's what you're doing-- the
这就是你在做的
primary piece of work that is
被请求的首要工作
being requested, and having a
这其中有一个副作用
Well, if no one was reading the
好 如果没有人读取
result of the side effect, then
这个副作用的结果
you're doing that work
那你就是在反复地
redundantly, over and over
进行多余的工作
You can often get a much more
你通常可以
efficient interface by using a
通过使用成批的接口
batch interface, where a client
得到一个更加有效的接口
gives you an array or some sort
在这里客户端会给你一系列的
of collection of all the work to
或者某种集合 包括所有要完成的工作
be done, so that you can compute
以便你能够一次性地
that side effect just once.
计算那个副作用
Now, sometimes you have many
那么 有时你有很多个客户端 对吗
And they can't batch across each
你无法对它们进行
other, and you can get even--
批量处理 那也没关系
you can still get that same
你仍然可以通过推迟工作
style of performance through
以及缓慢地进行工作
deferring the work and doing it
来获得一样的性能风格
A third easy way to improve
第三种提高你的性能的
performance is you look through
简单的方法
that instrument's trace, is to
是检查整个 Instruments 的轨迹
find areas where you see the
来寻找你看到它
same thing being computed over
对同样的东西进行反复计算
and over again.
的地方
For example, you have a method
比如说 有一个方法
in its computing, the size of
在它计算某个文档的大小的过程中
some text, then you see the same
你看到同样的事情
thing happening several frames
在之后的几帧中也出现了
later, for the same text, and
对于相同的文档
again, and again.
不断地重复
Now, in this situation, of
好 在这样的情况下
course, you want to try to just
当然 你肯定想
compute that value one time.
一次性计算出该值
Compute it at the top, and pass
在最顶端计算它
it down or maybe cache it.
让它不断地传下去 或者缓存它
Another technique you have
另一个你可以在你的
available in your UI
UI App 中使用的方法
applications is considering how
就是考虑
many views you are using to
你使用了多少视图
render your UI.
来渲染你的 UI
It can be very great for your
使用一些带有小的
source code organization to use
函数集的很小的视图
very small views, with small
然后再将它们一起
sets of functionality, and to
生成大的函数
compose them together into
以此来组织你的源代码
larger pieces.
这是很好的
But the more views you use, the
但是你使用的视图越多
harder you tax the rendering and
你就越难负担绘图
layout systems.
进行系统的布局
Now, this is a two-way street,
现在 这是一条双向道
because smaller views often led
因为更小的视图通常会
you to have more fine-grain
让你有更多精密的捕捉
caching, which can be good for
它们也可以提高你的性能
But generally, you can tweak the
但是一般来说 你可以微调
number of views that you have in
你拥有的视图的数量
order to have a significant
以对性能产生
impact on performance.
显著的影响
It is not always best to have
但视图更少的话
fewer views, otherwise all of
也并不都是最好的
our applications would just have
否则我们所有的 App
one giant view for the whole
都会只有一个包括所有内容的
thing.
巨大视图了
Another technique that comes up
另一个经常
pretty frequently is using
用到的方法就是直接观察
We often have two areas of our
我们的源代码中通常
source code that are loosely
有两个松散耦合的方面
Maybe one area knows about the
也许它们彼此知道对方
other, and they're communicating
而它们是通过一些
with each other through some
间接的机制
indirect mechanism.
进行交流的
Maybe they're using NS
也许它们用
Notification Center, some
NS Notification Center
block-based call backs,
一些基于代码块的回调
delegation, or key value
授权或者关键值观察
Now something that I see very
我常常见到
frequently is we'll have some
我们会有一些模型代码
model code, and it's going in a
它们在一个循环中
loop, being changed, and every
被不断地改变
time it is going to that loop,
而每次它走向循环
it is firing lots of KVO
就会引起许多 KVO 通告机制
You can't actually see that in
当然 你其实并不能
the model code, of course, but
在模块代码中看到它
over in some other controller,
但是在一些其他的控件里
it's madly responding and trying
它会十分活跃地作出回应
to keep up with whatever is
并试图与模块里的变化
changing in the model, and
保持一致
you're burning lots of CPU time
这时你就花费了许多 CPU 时间
doing this, that ends up being
最终当你考虑整个的
redundant when you consider the
变化的时候
whole scope of changes.
这些都是多余的工作
Now, if this was direct callouts
那么 如果这是模块代码中的
from the model code, either
直接调用 那么
through notifications,
不论是通过通告机制或授权
delegation or manual block-based
还是手动进行基于代码块的回调
call backs, it would be much
改变都会发生地更加明显
happening as you edited that
当你编辑该模块代码时
And you might decide that it is
你也许认为
totally appropriate to pull some
将一些通告机制从循环中
of those notifications out from
拖出到循环之外
inside the loop to outside the
以对性能产生
loop, to have a big impact on
较大的影响 是完全合适的
Now, alternatively, on the
那么 或者
controller side, you could use
在控件这边 你可以用这些
one of these deferring and
推迟和批量处理方法中的一个
batching techniques to avoid the
来避免多余的工作
redundant work and just not
只是它们的回应
respond synchronously.
是不同步的
Last, this is an easy one.
最后 这是最简单的一个
Once your code is already on the
一旦你的代码已经在
[inaudible] happy path, you
一个很好的路径上了
know, it's already linear, and
你知道 它已经是线性的了
it's not going to get any better
而且不会有比线性更好的了
That's sort of the minimum
这是一种你要
performance that you're going to
获得的最低性能
You're after all the constant
毕竟 你要尽可能地
time improvements that you can.
改进常数时间
Now, an easy one is that if
那么 很简单
you're using dictionaries like
如果你将词典
they were objects, then you
作为对象使用
probably know you're doing this,
那你或许已经看到这点
if you have a bunch of string
如果你有一堆为秘钥准备的
constants for all the keys, then
字符串常数
you can get a big improvement to
那么你就可以大幅度提高
code clarity, to code
代码的清晰性
completion, to re-factoring, to
提高代码完成和重构
making the validating your
以及源代码验证
source code, by using specific
通过使用特定的形式
It couldn't be easier with
用它们的 strucks 和 swift
strucks and swift with their
用它们隐含的初始化器和一致性
implicit initializers and
来平等哈希值
conformance to equitable hash.
这再简单不过了
And this can just be hands-down
而这能轻而易举地
an improvement to your source
改进你的源代码
code, and you'd be surprised at
如果你在许多小目标上
how much time you're spending in
完成数百万次的
string hashing and string
字符串哈希映射
equation if you were doing this
和字符串 equation 的话
millions of times on lots of
你会惊讶于你花费了
small objects.
多少时间
So with that, I'd like to turn
那么接下来的时间
it over to Matthew to talk to
我想请 Matthew 上台来
you about how we've applied
谈谈我们如何将这些方法
these techniques inside of
应用到“照片”中去
[ Applause ]
［ 掌声 ］
>> Thanks Jim.
>> 谢谢 Jim
Hi everyone.
大家好
I'm Matthew Lucas, an engineer
我是 Matthew Lucas
in the photos team, and today I
一名“照片”团队的工程师
want to give you some practical
今天我想给你们一些
examples on performance from
直接从“照片”中来的
directly from photos.
实用的性能的例子
So first, let's talk about
那么首先 让我们先来
photos for a second.
简单谈谈“照片”
We are all familiar with this
我们都十分熟悉这个 App
It lets you store, browse, and
它可以供你存储 浏览
experience your favorite
并体验你最喜爱的时刻
So you can browse your favorite
因此你可以浏览你最喜欢的时刻
moments from the moments view,
从这个“时刻”视图里
that you can see here.
在这里可以看到
It's is the default view.
这是默认视图
But you can also get another
但是你也可以
view from the collection, or the
切换到另一种视图“精选”
years.
或者“年度”
And I'll talk more about this
这个我一会再细说
Now, libraries today can go from
现在图片库里可以有
1,000 to 100,000 assets previous
1000 到 100000 张先前的素材
depending on your love for
这取决于你对拍照的喜爱
And we all love capturing those
我们都喜欢捕捉每天的生活中
fun and precious moments we live
那些快乐而珍贵的瞬间
So we are patient enough to
所以我们都很耐心地去捕捉它们
capture them, but we are less
但是当这样的事发生时
patient when something like this
我们并不是那么地有耐心
How would you feel if something
在你启动“照片”
moments like this would be
这个 App 的时候
displayed in Photos the first
如果你的“时刻”变成了这样
time you launch the app?
你会有什么感受
Now, you may also experience
那么 你也许
something like this, where we
还会遇到这样的情况
are showing a lot of
在这里只有许多的
placeholders, and that's really
空白图片框 这样看起来
not great.
并不是非常好
Maybe you're soft scrolling,
也许你轻轻滑动
you'll be lost in this gray
这个灰色的地方就会消失
area, the [inaudible] would
照片就会开始加载
keep scrolling and then you'll
但你继续滑动
experience some frame drops
你就会遇到一些掉帧
because the views are being
因为视图被更新了
Well, our goal is to not show
好 我们的目标就是
views like this.
不要出现这样的视图
We think this is not providing a
我们认为这种视图
great user experience, but we
并不是好的用户体验
understand that sometimes it's
但是我们知道有时候
unavoidable.
这是不可避免的
But when it's too frequent, this
但是当它过于频繁时
isn't really great.
就无法忍受了
Now, when you work on an app,
现在 当你运行一个 App 时
you want to make sure that it's
你想要确保它一开始就能用
responsive, and usable at once.
能够做出响应
You also want to make sure that
你还要确保
the animations are smooth.
动画是很流畅的
And these two attributes are
而这两个属性
really crucial to providing a
对用户体验来说
great user experience.
都是十分重要的
If the users don't find your app
如果用户发现你的 App
relatable or pertinent, they
并不相关
might stop using it.
他们也许不会再使用它了
Now, to illustrate these two
现在我来举例说明这两点
points, I would like to give you
我要给你们
two examples.
举两个例子
And the first one is going to be
第一个就是我们如何
how we optimize launching to
对这个“时刻”视图的启动
this moment view.
进行优化
The second one is how we build
第二个则是我们如何
the collections and years view
创建这个“精选”和“年度”视图
for good scrolling preference.
以更好地适应用户的偏好
First, let's do launching
首先是启动“时刻”
[inaudible].
[ 音质不清晰 ]
So what is launch?
那么什么是启动
There are three kinds of
我们有三种启动
The first and more expensive one
第一种也是更为昂贵的一种
is the find referred as called,
即我们所说的冷启动
and it depends the first time
它取决于在重启后
you are going to relaunch your
第一次重新启动你的 App
So basically, nothing has been
所以里面基本上
cached yet, and it might require
还没有缓存任何东西
some bug run processes or some
也许你需要载入一些后台过程
libraries to load.
或者一些库
Now, it also happens when the
下面在这样的情况也会冷启动
system goes under memory
系统在内存压力下运行
pressure and starts reclaiming
开始回收一些内存
Now, if you kill an app, it
那么 如果你关闭一个 App
might not trigger a code launch,
也许不会触发代码运行
because the system decides when
因为是系统决定了资源
the resources should be paged
应该何时被放在
out.
页面上
And when you kill an app, and
而如果你关闭了一个 App
you relaunch it a few second
然后几秒之后重新打开它
later, it's almost guaranteed
几乎可以肯定
that you'll hit a warm launch.
你进行的是一个热启动
And we call it warm, because the
我们称其为热启动
resources or the dependents are
是因为资源或从属的东西
still in the cache, so it's
都仍然在缓存里
faster to launch.
所以它能更快地启动
Now, the last type is-- we call
那么 最后一种类型就是
it hot, and it's basically a
我们所说的热启动
resume, because it's when your
根本上说它就是继续启动
app is already running and is
因为这时 App 已经处于运行状态
being brought back to the
直接把它带回前台就可以了
So when you start measuring
所以当你开始测量启动时
launch, you should start by
你应该从测量
measuring the warm launch.
热启动开始
And the time it takes to launch
它所用的时间
during this warm is less
要比冷启动所花的时间
variable than the cold launch,
变量更小
and the test iteration is much
而测试迭代也更快
faster as you don't need to
因为你不需要
reboot your device.
重启你的设备
Now, the way we measure launch
那么 我们用来测量启动的方法
is by evaluating the time it
是对从你点击这个 App
takes from the moment you hit
的图标的那一刻
the application icon, and until
到你可以开始与你的 App 进行互动
you can start interacting with
的整个时间进行评估
And what I mean by interacting
我说互动的意思就是
is that it's really using and
它真的可以使用了
not interacting with a spinner.
而不再有旋转的圈
A common pattern is to dispatch
它通常会在显示
some work and display a spinner
这个旋转的圈的同时
in the meantime, well that
分派一些工作
doesn't make the app usable
但并不能让 App 更快地投入使用
sooner, so we are trying to
所以我们想要
avoid that here.
避免这些
Now there are three goals that
现在 我们有三个针对
we are shooting for at Photos,
“照片”的目标
and the first one is that we
第一个就是我们想要瞬时
want to instant, we don't want
我们不想出现任何
to display any spinner, and we
等待的圆圈
placeholder or [inaudible].
空白的图片框
And I Have to be honest with
坦白地说
you, we-- you might see some
你也许会看到一些空白图片框
placeholders the first time you
在你第一次
synchronize with iClub, but when
同步 iClub 的时候
the data is local, we really try
但是当数据本地化后
our best to not display any.
就尽可能地不显示了
Now, what do we mean by instant?
那么 我所说的瞬时是什么意思呢
Well, the time it takes to
就是它启动所花的时间
launch should be the same time
应该和从主屏幕上
as the zoom animation from the
放大的动画过程的时间 保持一致
That is usually between 500 and
这个时间通常是 500 到
600 milliseconds, and that way,
600 毫秒之间
the transition from the home
这样一来 从主屏幕到
screen to the application is
App 的转换
seamless for the user, and the
就是无缝连接的了
user can start interacting with
用户可以立刻与 App 互动
it, as soon as the animation is
只要它显示完动画过程
And by the way, this is the
顺便说一下
lowest recommendation, not
这是最基本的建议
something just for photos, so
这不只是给“照片”的
it's valid for any apps.
所以它适用于所有的 App
Now, let's look at how photos
那么让我们来看看“照片”
launches today.
现在是如何启动的
If we look more closely at what
如果我们近距离地
is happening exactly, you can
看看到底发生了什么
see that photos is all set up
你就能看到“照片”
and ready before the animation
在动画过程完成之前
is done.
就已经准备好了
And if we dive into the launch
如果我们深入剖析这个启动
anatomy, you will see there is
我们就会看到
mainly two parts.
这里主要有两个部分
The first part is being spent in
第一部分时间花在 DYD 中
DYD, this is the loader that is
这是载入器
going to load and link all of
它将加载并连接
your dependent libraries, but
你所有的动态链接器
it's also going to run your
而它还要运行你的
static initializers.
静态初始化器
And your control over that part
虽然你对这部分
is limited, but it's not
的控制是有限的
impossible.
但也有可能做到
I would encourage you to watch
我鼓励你们去看看
the DYD session from last year
去年 DYD 的部分
in order to get more details on
就能得到这个方面
that part.
更多的细节
Now DYD is also calling Main in
那么 DYD 也要
your object table, which leads
在你的项目表中调用 Main
us to the second part here,
这就将我们带到了第二个部分
where you have lots of control
在这里你有很多控件
over, and this part, you need to
这个部分里 你需要确保
make sure that it stays under
将它的时间保持在
500 milliseconds.
500 毫秒以内
Now, the first [inaudible] pass
现在 第一个布局正好被排在
after the Did Finish launching
Did Finish Launching 之后
will mark the end of your
它将标记启动的结束
launch, and this is basically
而这时你基本上
when your app should be usable.
就可以使用你的 App 了
There are a few principles that
在这个部分
we will be referring to during
我们将要提到
this session, and these are
一些原则
really the common pillars of the
它们的确是我们在
performance work that we
进行性能工作时
achieved.
最大的收获
The first one is that we want to
第一是我们需要惰性
be lazy and defer the work that
推迟我们不需要
we don't need.
的工作
The second one is that we want
第二则是要积极主动
to be proactive, and it's valid
而这两个方面
for two things.
都有它的效用
It's valid for being proactive
积极主动能够
in order to anticipate the work
十分有效地预料
that we are making it later, we
我们之后要做的工作
also want to be proactive and
我们想要积极主动地
catch regressions quickly, so
快速捕捉到衰退
you should make sure that you
因而你要确保
have continuous integration
你设置了连续的综合测试
And the last point is we want to
最后一点就是
be constant, regardless of the
无论我们总共需要
total amount of data that we
加载多少数据
need to load.
我们都要持续不变
Now, if we were taking a nave
现在 如果我们用这个方法
approach, and we were loading
我们载入所有在启动中
everything we needed during
要用到的东西
launch, this is how long it
这是它大概会在一个
would take roughly for a 30,000
有 30000 项的库里
item library.
花费的时间
First you need to initialize the
首先你需要初始化数据库
database, then you need to
然后你需要
prepare some view controllers.
准备一些视图控件
You need to configure the data
接着需要配置数据资源
sources, load some library
加载一些库图像
images, and fetch the cloud
然后读取云状态
And keep in mind that this might
你要记住 这个时间也许会
vary as the data grow, and in
随着数据的生长发生变化
fact, the data will grow forever
而其实数据将会一直生长
as people takes pictures every
只要人们每天都拍照
So at Photos, really keep in
所以在“照片”里一定要记住
mind that we are dealing with a
我们要处理的是没有边界的
non-bonded data sets.
数据集
Now, let's see how we optimize
那么让我们来看看
each of these steps for Photos,
如何优化“照片”的每一个步骤
and let's start with
就让我们从初始化数据库开始
So first, usually, the database
首先 数据库通常
is initialized and loaded when
是在执行第一个查询的时候
the first query is being fired.
被初始化和载入的
One optimization that we have
我们发现了一个非常
found was to do it as early as
值得优化的地方 就是尽快地
possible in the background
在后台线程中完成初始化
thread, so that it doesn't have
这样它就不需要
to do the initialization when
在执行第一个查询时
the first query has been fired.
再进行初始化工作了
And this is an issue, especially
这是个问题 特别是
if the first query is being done
如果第一个查询已经
from the main thread.
从主线程当中完成了
Now, we spend a lot of time and
现在 我们已经花了很多时间
we are still spending a lot of
而我们仍要花费很多时间
time reviewing all the queries
来检查我们在启动过程中的
that we're doing during launch,
所有的查询
and we want to make sure that
我们想要确保
the work that we are doing is
我们正在做的工作
only the necessary one, and we
是必要的
are not doing more.
我们不再做更多的工作
Now, lastly, we want to ensure
那么最后 我们要确保
that all the queries that we are
我们所做的所有查询
doing are efficient as possible,
都要尽可能地高效
and we want to avoid the complex
我们也想尽可能地
query as much as possible as
避免复杂的查询
And we sometimes we understand
我们有时知道
that we need this, and for these
我们需要这样做 针对这类情况
cases, we are setting up some
我们设置了一些索引
indexes, so that we can speed
以便我们能提高速度
Now we are aiming for, at most,
现在我们的目标是
30 milliseconds spent in that
在初始化上花费的时间
initialization.
不超过 30 毫秒
So next, let's look at how we
那么接下来让我们看看
are preparing our view
我们如何准备视图控件
So we have four tabs
这里我们有四个标记
representing the main features
呈现在 App 的
of the app.
主要特性上
And so the first thing that we
那么我们需要注意的第一件事
need to be careful of is we want
就是我们想要
to minimize the work that is
通过做最少的工作
being done in the initialization
来初始化这三个
of these three non-visible ones,
不可见的标记
and the rule that we are trying
这里我们要遵循的原则
to follow here is to do as
就是做尽可能地
little work as possible in the
少的工作来进行初始化
We really want to do the bare
我们想要将工作最小化
minimum, and note all the data
同时记录载入的视图中的
in the view that loads.
所有的数据
This also allows us to
这也让我们可以
initialize our controllers in
在恒定时间内
constant time.
初始化我们的控件
Now, lastly, we also want to
那么最后 我们想要
ensure that only the visible
确保我们只加载了可见视图
It's easy, and we often regress
这很简单 而我们通常是
on that part, so you should
在那个部分出现衰退的
really be careful about that.
因此你应该格外小心
So preparing the view
那么在准备视图控件的工作上
controllers, we are now aiming
我们现在的目标是
for 120 milliseconds.
花费 120 毫秒
But preparing view controllers
但是准备视图控件意味着
implies configuring the data
要配置数据资源
sources, and let's look at that
接下来我们就来看这一块
So the Moments view is a
所以在“时刻”视图里
representation of these things,
会呈现出这些东西
events in your life, and the UI
呈现你生活中的事件
represents that by having this
而 UI 则通过获得
group of photos, and these
这组照片来呈现出
headers.
这些标题栏
In this library, for example, we
比如说在这个图库中
might have 500 moments, and in
我们也许有 500 张照片
order to build a view, we need
为了创建一个视图
to load all the moments up
我们需要预先加载所有的图片
But the only thing we need
但是我们只是需要
really for these moments is only
这些照片的元数据
the meta data so we can build
这样我们就可以创建视图了
We don't need your content.
我们不需要你的内容
So the first thing we do is we
因此我们首先要做的就是
fire that query, which is super
执行那个超高速的询问
And then we are only loading the
然后我们只加载
content that we need here.
我们这里需要的内容
In that case here, we are only
既然是这样
going to load the visible
我们只要加载可见内容
content, which in our case is
在我们这个例子里
going to be between 7 to 10
可见内容在 7 到 10 个图片之间
Since our deficit is limited,
因为我们的可见内容
and finite, we can allow
是有限值 所以我们可以
ourselves to do it synchronously
在主线程上
on the main thread.
同时进行加载
Now, we also want to anticipate
同时 我们还想预先安排工作
and schedule the work so that we
这样我们就可以
can start loading the remaining
开始异步加载
data as synchronously.
剩下的数据
And we do that on the bug run
我们在后台线程上
thread, with the right quality
以正确的特性进行加载
of service to make sure that it
来确保它不会
doesn't preempt the main thread
抢占主线程的运行
Now we are aiming at 100
在这里我们的目标是
milliseconds here.
100 毫秒
So lastly, our data sources are
那么最后 我们的数据源
also providing some images and
还提供一些图像
let's see how we optimize that
我们来看看如何优化这个部分
So this was by far the biggest
所以目前为止
chunk here that we are all
这是我们面对的
attacking, and when we realized
最大的数据块
that we were spending multiple
当我们意识到在启动时
seconds loading this image
我们花费了好几秒的时间
during launch, we realized that
来加载这个图像 我们就意识到
we were doing too much work.
我们做了太多的工作
So the first thing that we did
所以我们所做的第一件事
is that we evaluated the number
就是估计我们在启动时
of images that we needed during
需要用到多少张图像
launch, and we are only loading
然后在第一个事务中
that during that first
我们只加载那些图像
In that case, that can be up to
这种情况下 这一数量
60 including some piling above
可以达到 60 张
and below.
包括上下堆起的
And next, in order to load those
接下来 为了先加载那些图像
images firstly, we need to make
我们需要确保
sure that we are all loading
我们只加载
only low-resolutions one.
低分辨率的图像
That way we are loading fewer
这样我们加载在
pixels in memory, and it is much
内存里的像素就越少
more efficient.
这样就能更高效
That chunk is now representing
呈现出这个数据块
200 milliseconds.
现在需要 200 毫秒
And this is, by far, the biggest
这是目前为止
gain that we had.
我们提速最多的部分
Which I need to be a constant
我要它成为一个常数时间
time, and that's really great.
真的很不错
Now, sometimes you have to ask
那么 有时候你禁不住
yourself the question, is this
问问自己这个问题
really needed during launch?
这在启动的时候真的需要吗
And one of our examples here is
我们这里的一个例子
this footer view.
是页脚视图
That pulls information via the
它通过网络或数据库
network or the database, and
来搜集信息
literally first our design was
而其实我们最先的设计
to not show it during launch.
是不要在启动时显示它
To prioritize all the images
以优先所有我们
that we are seeing here.
在这里看到的图像
We wanted to show as much images
我们想要显示尽可能多的图像
So that may be simpler.
那这样可能就更简单了
We are now only scheduling that
我们现在只要安排
work post-launch, and we cache
启动后的工作
to process information for
我们缓存并加工之后要
raising later.
显示的信息
Now, if we would have had the
现在 如果我们已经需要
requirement of displaying this
显示这个信息
information, one approach could
有一个方法可以办到
have been to leverage the
利用后台来
register background at refresh
从 UA 工具包中
API from UA kit, that will
刷新 API
proactively clear your app so
它便会主动清除你的 App
that you can start preparing
这样当用户要启动 App 的时候
some content when the user is
你就可以开始
going to launch your app.
准备一些内容了
So now, that part has gone from
所以现在 这个部分已经从启动中删除了
launch, and that saves us 400
为我们节省了 400 秒的
milliseconds of CPU time.
CPU 时间
If we look at the updated
现在我们看这里的
breakdown here, we can see that
更新后的分解图
we now have only 450
可以看到这些工作
milliseconds worth of work.
只值得花费 450 毫秒
We are now fitting into that 500
而我们现在在这个 500 毫秒
millisecond time window, and
窗口之中
regardless of how things can be
而且不论如何
represented concurrently here,
将其同时呈现出来
the most important part of that
最重要的是
is to really make sure that you
一定要确保
think about the cost of
你要考虑你
preparing your content.
准备内容的时间成本
And what I mean by think is
我这里说的考虑
really measure it.
是要真的去测量它
Now, you should strive for doing
现在 你应该争取
work in constant time,
在常量时间里进行工作
regardless of the total amount
无论你加载的
of data you are loading.
数据总共有多少
In our case, really have
在我们的例子里
unbonded data assets, and we
我们的确有许多数据集
need to stay constant.
我们需要保持常量时间
Now that we have launched the
既然我们已经启动了 App
app, we need to start using it.
我们要开始使用它
And let's see how we did
那么我们来看看我们是
collections and [inaudible] for
如何创建“精选”和“年度”视图的
good [inaudible] performance.
以便我们提高性能
So as I mentioned earlier, our
正如我之前提到过
users can seamlessly transition
我们的用户能够进行
with animation from the Moments,
从动画过程到“时刻”视图的无缝转换
through the collections, to the
再通过“精选”
years view.
到“年度”视图
And this is a complex hierarchy.
这是一个复杂的层级
We have thousands of pictures to
我们要展示数千张的照片
We need to support live updates,
我们要支持实时更新
we need to also support
我们也要支持
animation between these layers,
这些图层间的动画过程
and we also have some gestures.
我们还有一些手势
Now, we also have some goals
那么 我们这里还有一些目标
For the experience we want to
对于带给我们用户的体验
The first one is the same as
第一个和之前一样
before, we don't want to have
我们不想有任何
any spinner.
等待的圆圈
We don't want to have
我们不想有空白的图片框
placeholders, but we also want
当然我们想要
to have smooth animations.
流畅的动画过程
And by smooth animations, I mean
这里所说的流畅
60 or 120 frames per second,
是指 60 到 120 帧每秒
depending on the screen you're
这依赖于你正在运行的屏幕
Now, remember the principles
记得之前我们说过的原则
Well, they are all applicable
现在 它们在这里都是有用的
We want to be lazy and defer the
我们想要懈怠并推迟
work we donate up front.
我们预先递交的工作
We want to be proactive, and
我们想要积极地
catch regressions quickly, but
快速捕捉衰退
we also want to be constant in
但是我们也想要
our layout passes, and
在布局关口中保持不变
regardless of a lot of data that
无论我们要加载多少数据
Now, this time, we also want to
那么 这次我们还想要及时
be timely, and we want to
我们想要记住
remember the rendering loop
绘制循环周期
And what I mean by that is that
这里我的意思是
I want you to remember that we
你要记住
only have 8 or 16 milliseconds
我们只有 8 或 16 毫秒
to render that frame, so we need
来绘制那一帧
to make sure that we are not
所以我们需要确保
going over that time, otherwise
我们不超时
we would start dropping frames.
否则就会开始掉帧
Now, let's take a step back, and
现在 让我们返回一步
look at what we are trying to
看看我们要在这里
achieve here.
获取什么
We wanted to have this portable
我们要这个便捷视图
view, with sections and mini
里面有分栏和小单元格
And that is basically what your
而这基本上就是
Collection view is providing,
“精选”视图给你提供的
right?
对吗
Except that in this extreme
只不过在这样极端的例子里
case, we are restricting the
我们会限制
limit of what we could achieve
我们使用这个基本的方法
with a basic approach.
可以获得的极限
And that resulted in too many
那样就会导致过多的
views, too many layers.
视图和过多的图层
But also in an increased layered
但是随着分层的复杂性不断增加
complexity, and that also had an
花在内存上的时间
increased memory cost.
也在不断增加
So we needed to innovate here,
所以这里我们需要创新
and we did that by restricting
我们大幅地限制视图的数量
the number of views drastically
同时仍使用一个
while still using a collection
“精选”视图
We used a technique more
我们使用的这种方法
commonly used in video games,
在电子游戏里更为常见
that is called atlasing.
它叫做图谱法
And it basically consists of
它基本上就是
combining a set of images into a
把一组图像组合
single one.
成为一个
We do that efficiently by using
我们高效地完成了它
only very small thumbnails
开始只用很小的缩略图
first, then we stamp all the raw
然后我们将所有的原始图像数据
image data on the canvas we are
标记在一个我们用作
using as a strip.
带状的画布上
Now, we use image raw data so
接着 我们使用图像原始数据
that we can avoid decoding each
这样就能够避免去解码每一个
thumbnail as we send.
我们发送的缩略图
So basically we are displaying a
因此基本上我们会显示一条
random strip of images.
随机的图像
Now, we generate and cache them
那么 我们飞速生成并缓存它们
on the fly so that we can be
因此我们可以更加灵活
And as we render multiple images
当我们将多个图片绘制成一个时
into a single one, we are
我们会大量寄存
registering the number of cells,
单元格 图层及目标的数量
which simplifies the layout and
这样便简化了布局
the time spent building it.
节省了创建它要花费的时间
Now, the separate works well,
现在这样很好
but it has trade offs to
但是也要有所取舍
consider as well, and this is
这就是它们的其中一个
So if someone tries to long
如果有人试着长按
press or force search an item
或强制搜索一个这里的项目
here, we will need to figure its
我们就需要计算它的位置
position so that we can achieve
这样我们才能
the preview correctly.
正确地获得预览
And as we display a single
因为只要我们显示一张图像
image, we need to maintain the
我们就需要维持
mapping of each individual
每个图像的映射
image, and its render strip.
以及它的绘制条
Now, you might be thinking, why
现在你也许在想
are we generating them on the
我们为什么要飞速地生成它们
Well, we need to support live
我们要支持实时更新
updates, that's the reason.
这就是原因
We need also to support
我们也需要不一样的视图大小
For example, we have landscape
比如说 我们这里有风景图
But we also have portraits.
但也有人像图
And also we can do that because
但是这没有关系
we can [inaudible] because our
因为我们的用户增长
user's labor typically grows
在很长一段时间里
organically over a long period
是十分典型的
of time, and the cases where we
而我们需要生成
might need to generate thousands
数千张图像这样的例子
of them are pretty rare.
相当地罕见
Now, you may be wondering also
现在 你或许想知道
why are we not generating the
那我们为什么不生成
whole section then?
整个这部分呢
Well the answer is that our
答案就是我们的设计记录
design record is to do this cool
就是完成这个动画过程
animation, where you can see
在这里你能看到
that the collections are
在“精选”视图中它们
expanding into their own
都扩展到自己的那部分中
sections or collapsing into
或者相反地
group ones, and the other way
折叠进它们的小组里
So if there is one thing that
所以如果说第二部分里
you should also remember from
你只要记住一件事情
that second part is you should
那就是你应该考虑
really think about the layout
你的层级的布局成本
course of your hierarchy and
然后对它进行测量
Lastly, you should always think
最后 你要时刻考虑性能
At Photos, we care deeply about
在“照片”里我们十分关心这点
it, and this is really part of
这正是我们日常工作的一部分
For more information, you can
要了解更多的信息
come and see us in these three
你们可以观看我在这里提到的
labs that are mentioned here,
三个实验室
and I hope that you have a great
祝你们
conference.
参会愉快
Thank you.
谢谢
[ Applause ]
［ 掌声 ］